

# VADYM HOPKO

Front-End Developer

# **ABOUT ME**

I was born on August 10, 1990. Front-End for me is both a job and a hobby, so even in my off-hours I am engaged in development. I like to create the most convenient interaction between users and website or web-application. I plan to become a Senior Front-End Developer in a 5 years

#### **SKILLS**

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- Vue.js
- Git
- Gulp
- Sass
- Bootstrap
- SVG
- Node.js
- jQuery
- Figma
- English Pre-Intermediate

# **CONTACT**

Email: gopko.vadim@gmail.com

Phone: +1 (808) 428 - 5781

Website: vadymhopko.github.io/portfolio Address: Kapaia street, Honolulu, HI

96825

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Vice-rector's assistant**

I.I. Mechnikov Odesa National University | January 2014 - January 2015

- Created student organizations
- Accepted appeals to the Vice-rector
- Worked on the preparation of meetings and sessions held by the Vice-rector

## **Top manager**

Interwindows, engineering company | February 2020 - June 2021

- Presented the company's services to developers
- Made commercial offers

#### Freelancer

Vip orders - Freelance websites | January 2022 - Present

- Web/Mobile design
- Responsive websites development
- Search Engine Optimization (SEO)
- Setting up hosting and domain name

# **EDUCATION**

# I.I. Mechnikov Odesa National University

Expert | 2007 - 2012

- Faculty of Economics and Law
- Specialty: "Jurisprudence"
- Qualification: "Lawyer"

# COURSES

### Hillel IT School

FrontEnd Developer | 2021 - 2021

- Course Front-End Basic | March 2021 June 2021
- Course Front-End Pro | August 2021 December 2021

#### **Graduate Certificates**

- https://certificate.ithillel.ua/view/97046686
- https://certificate.ithillel.ua/view/86477844